http://www.alleybaggett.net/support/terms.html

PERSONAL NOTE
Any regular visitor of my website knows that I own the images and content available on my website. I have invested a lot of time and money trying to make my website the best possible for my fans. However, the widespread unauthorized use of my name and images on the Internet is greatly affecting my ability to present you with the best and most enjoyable website. Moreover, a number of people are using my name and image to commercially exploit my fans while trading off my name and image that I have worked so hard to establish. Over the years, I have attempted to stop such unauthorized use of my name and image and many of my fans have supported my efforts by kepping me informed regarding sites that use or trade my images. To assist me in these efforts, I have retained Dennis L. Wilson, an attorney specializing in Internet law, to assist me in stopping the unauthorized use of my name and images. Hopefully, my efforts will result in a better official website for all my fans. Thank you for all your support. If you wish to use either my name or image on your website, please contact me for authorization.
AGE AND LEGAL ACCESS CERTIFICATION
The content in the www.alleybaggett.net members area contains nudity and is intended for a mature, consenting audience. To purchase a membership, you must be of legal age to view such material in the area in which you live. We are not responsible for minors posing as adults. By subscribing to www.alleybaggett.net, you certify that you are 18 years of age or older; that you are familiar with all local laws in your area affecting your legal right to access erotica or adult-oriented materials; that you have the legal right to access adult-oriented materials and www.alleybaggett.net has the legal right to transmit them to you; that you are requesting adult-oriented materials for your own private enjoyment and that you will never share these materials with a minor or in ANY WAY make these materials available to a minor.
COPYRIGHT
Except for public domain material and electronic messages, all materials on www.alleybaggett.net are protected by Federal copyright and are protected under treaty provisions and worldwide copyright laws. Materials contained in any part of www.alleybaggett.net may not be reproduced, copied, edited, published, transmitted or uploaded in any way without the written permission of www.alleybaggett.net and it's respective owner (i.e. photographs found on www.alleybaggett.net shot by Photographers working with Alley Baggett). Except as expressly stated in the Limited License provision in these Terms of Use, www.alleybaggett.net does not grant any express or implied right to you under any of his/her trademarks, service marks, copyrights or other proprietary information.
LIMITED
LICENSE
www.alleybaggett.net provides the materials on this site for the personal, non-commercial use by visitors of www.alleybaggett.net. Your account and password are for you, and you alone! Sharing, selling, or giving away your username and password is prohibited. Also, re-distribution of members area material on the Internet, Usenet, BBS or other archive collections, will cause your account to be immediately terminated with no refund, and legal action taken if necessary. Visitors of www.alleybaggett.net are granted a single copy license to download (on a single computer only) or print one copy of any of the information made available for downloading found on this site for personal, non-commercial use only. www.alleybaggett.net reserves the right to limit the amount of materials downloaded. Commercial use of www.alleybaggett.net, or any material located on it, is strictly prohibited. In addition, users of www.alleybaggett.net may not: (i) modify any of the materials found in any area of www.alleybaggett.net; (ii) use any of the materials found in any area of www.alleybaggett.net for any public display, performance, sale or rental; (iii) remove, modify or alter any copyright or other proprietary notice, or trademarks from any of the materials found in any area of www.alleybaggett.net; or (iv) otherwise transfer any material located in any area of www.alleybaggett.net to any other person or entity. www.alleybaggett.net reserves the right to terminate this license at any time if you breach or violate any provision of this Terms of Use agreement, in which case you will be obligated to immediately destroy any information or materials you have downloaded, printed or otherwise copied from this site. www.alleybaggett.net reserves all other rights coincident or related to this site.
COMMUNICATIONS NOT PRIVATE
www.alleybaggett.net does not provide any facility for sending or receiving private or confidential electronic communications. All messages transmitted to www.alleybaggett.net shall be deemed to be readily accessible to the general public. Visitors should not use www.alleybaggett.net to transmit any communication for which the sender intends only the sender and the intended recipient(s) to read. Notice is hereby given that all messages entered into www.alleybaggett.net can and may be read by the operators of this service, regardless of whether or the operators are the intended recipients of such messages.
DISCLAIMER
THE MATERIALS ON www.alleybaggett.net ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. www.alleybaggett.net OFFERS NO ASSURANCE OF UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE SERVICE. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR BROWSER PROBLEMS, INCOMPATIBLE SOFTWARE, POOR CONNECTIONS, OR INTERNET SERVICE OUTAGES THAT MAY INTERFERE WITH INDIVIDUAL MEMBERS' ABILITY TO ACCESS THE SITE. www.alleybaggett.net DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE INFORMATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, LINKS OR OTHER ITEMS CONTAINED ON THIS WEB SITE. www.alleybaggett.net MAY CHANGE ANY OF THE INFORMATION FOUND AT THIS SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. www.alleybaggett.net MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE THE INFORMATION FOUND AT THIS SITE. IN NO EVENT SHALL www.alleybaggett.net BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE MATERIAL OR INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE, EVEN IF www.alleybaggett.net HAS BEEN ADVISED OF SUCH DAMAGES. (BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.) WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO TERMINATE AN ACCOUNT THAT HAS BEEN DELIBERATELY ABUSED BY A USER. www.alleybaggett.net MEMBERS WHO ARE WITH THE SITE FOR MORE THEN 30 DAYS WILL BE CONSIDERED LOYAL MEMBERS AND WILL BE REWARDED WITH ADDITIONAL CONTENT IN OUR LOYAL MEMBERS SECTION. CERTAIN UPDATES ON OUR WEBSITE ARE FOR LOYAL MEMBERS ONLY. NEW MEMBERS WILL GET ACCESS TO ALL THE OTHER CONTENT EXCLUDING THE LOYAL MEMBERS SECTION UNTIL QUALIFICATION REQUIREMENTS ARE MET.
LINKS TO THIS SITE
You may establish a hypertext "link" to this site and/or distribute, modify or re-use the text or graphics of this site only after obtaining written permission from www.alleybaggett.net allowing you to do so.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES
This site contains links to sites which are controlled by third parties. Those linked sites are not under the control of www.alleybaggett.net, and www.alleybaggett.net is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a link site. www.alleybaggett.net is providing those links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by www.alleybaggett.net of any linked site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
JURISDICTION AND VENUE
This site is controlled and operated by Baggett Enterprises and its representatives from their offices in Los Angeles, California, United States of America. They make no representation that the materials available on this site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to them from jurisdictions where their contents are illegal is prohibited. These provisions of this Terms of Use are to be governed and construed by California law. In the event of a dispute arising out of or relating to this Terms of Use, or your use of or access to this site, litigation must be brought in state or federal court in the City and County of Los Angeles, California.
PRIVACY POLICY
What kind of information do you collect?
When you purchase the membership portion of our web site www.alleybaggett.net, you are asked to provide your name, address, e-mail, username and password, credit card number and expiration date, securely through CCBILL, our designated Access Management provider. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account.
Please read the Terms & Conditions along with the Privacy Policy for my Online Store by clicking here.
Who sees my information?
Baggett Enterprises is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not, and will not, distribute, sell, share, or rent any personally identifiable information to third parties without your express consent, other than as necessary to process your credit card payment.(1)
You can view CCBILL's Privacy Policy by clicking here.
How do you use my information?
We use you information solely in order to facilitate your viewing of our web site and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and web site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us.
We do not provide your e-mail to third parties without your express consent.
You can view CCBILL's Terms and Conditions by clicking here.
I’ve got more questions – can you help?
Baggett Enterprises recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this web site or your dealings with www.alleybaggett.net, please contact our:
webmaster
@
alleybaggett.net
.
Please note that persons under the age of 18 are prohibited from viewing our website, and www.alleybaggett.net does not collect any personal information from persons under the age of 18. Please also note that www.alleybaggett.net is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of web sites to which it may provide links or the websites of its advertisers.
(1) Unless requested via a subpoena, court order, or local, state, federal or
international law enforcement request.
NOTICES
Notices by www.alleybaggett.net to customers shall be given by means of electronic messages or by a general posting on the site. Notices by customers to www.alleybaggett.net shall be given by electronic messages unless otherwise specified in the agreement. All questions, complaints, or notices to www.alleybaggett.net, by means of electronic message must be sent to our webmaster
@
alleybaggett.net
I FULLY AGREE WITH THESE TERMS & CONDITIONS     |     I DISAGREE
Warning:
This site contains nudity and is intended for adults over the age of 18.
Copyright © 1998-2015 www.AlleyBaggett.net, All Rights Reserved. All models are 18 or over and in full compliance with 18 U.S.C. 2257
